# **GREY HARDY**

678-743-1785 ♦ greyhardy7@gmail.com ♦ linkedin.com/in/greyhardy ♦ itsgreyedout.github.io/ ♦ github.com/ltsGreyedOut

#### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Forward-thinking and agile transformation leader with expertise in aligning people, processes and technology to deliver strategies and technical solutions that drive revenue growth, increase capacity and ensure business continuity. Highly successful in identifying trends and facilitating enterprise-wide change initiatives that positively impact performance, mitigate risk and enhance the customer experience. A trusted leader and communicator; able to influence executive decision making, build consensus with cross-divisional partners and create collaborative work cultures that maximize individuals' strengths and empower professional growth.

#### **CAREER HIGHLIGHTS**

### **Organizational Effectiveness**

 As the Manager of Enterprise Applications at Cox Enterprises; increased department capacity and performance 300%, by cross-training team members on all department functions, standardizing processes and streamlining off-shore and vendor resources.

### **Risk Management**

 Within an aggressive timeline, automated Cox Enterprises' vulnerability management process to drive efficiency improvements and deliver over \$30K in annual cost savings. Subsequently template was adopted across divisions with similar success.

### **Resource Management**

 Reduced Cox Enterprise Applications' operational costs \$200k and significantly improved the performance of an offshore consulting team by influencing the third party provider's leadership to fund training and certification programs for their contracted staff.

#### **Inclusion Leadership**

Hand-selected by Cox Automotive's executive team to serve as the primary spokesperson, founder and co-chair for
a diversity and inclusion enterprise-wide resource group (ERG). Played a leadership role in positioning DEI as a
corporate priority by establishing the ERG leadership team and creating plans, objectives and KPIs that aligned
business strategies with inclusion and diversity initiatives. Additionally chosen as an Ambassador for THRIVE, an ERG
for next generation leaders.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### COX ENTERPRISES, INC., Atlanta, GA

2006-present

### Manager, Enterprise Applications, Cox Enterprises (2017-present)

Selected to turn-around and grow this under-performing department. Manage a 24/7 globally dispersed operation of enterprise application administrators and Microsoft SQL DBAs who serve as business analysts to the entire Cox organization. Identify and oversee vendor relationships to include contract negotiations, budget control (\$500k), strategic alignment and performance management. Deliver, maintain and operate high-availability and reliable systems (Control-M and Microsoft SQL) to support critical operations. Develop and modify the department's risk management and business continuity plans.

- Influenced cross-divisional department leaders to utilize Control-M, a workload automation platform for their business processes that ensured consistent on-time delivery, increased capacity and reduced labor costs. Additionally, this service created multiple revenue streams for the department to deliver over \$100K.
- In the midst of the COVID pandemic, introduced fun and interactive team building and employee engagement activities that boosted morale, maintained productivity levels and reduced operating expense.
- Promoted cross-divisional alignment and collaboration by partnering with another manager to institute monthly training meetings that focused on better communications and best practice sharing for workload automation.
- Prepared the company to expediently respond to the pandemic and other business disruptions by establishing a shared centralized location for departmental IT continuity plans.

GREY HARDY page 2

## **COX ENTERPRISES, INC. (continued)**

**Problem Manager, Cox Automotive** (2015-2017)

As part of a professional development plan, moved into this position with responsibility for leading the IT team
through crisis situations. Provided responsive, clear and ongoing communications to all levels of the organization,
including the C-suite. Following each event, oversaw efforts to identify root causes and ensure preventive measures
were completed within agreed upon timelines. Integrated newly acquired businesses into Cox's IT Service
Management Portfolio. Planned, delivered and supported IT services via people, processes and technology.

- Expanded partnerships with business leaders across divisions to deliver strategic solutions that drove transformation, improved productivity and streamlined business operations.
- Collaboratively wrote departmental incident and problem management SOPs; which enhanced new employee onboarding efforts, boosted performance and ensured consistency in service delivery.
- In response to ongoing service outages; created dashboards that monitored outstanding action items and provided executives with real time information to enable more informed decision making.

### Founding Co-Chair, Employee Resource Group (ERG), Cox Automotive (2016-2017)

While retaining full responsibility as the Problem Manager; founded and oversaw ERG affairs, strategic direction and annual plans with a leadership team of 10. Partnered with key stakeholders across multiple business units. Functioned as a DEI Ambassador, representing Cox at numerous sponsorship events. Led ERG Leadership Council meetings.

- Within 30 days, grew membership to 160 employees through marketing and outreach events and also facilitated the expansion to two remote ERG locations.
- Instrumental in moving the company to 17<sup>th</sup> place on *DiversityInc's* "Top 50 Places to Work" in 2017.
- Influenced key decision makers to expand healthcare benefits to include fertility and trans & non-binary healthcare.
- Advocated for all ERGs; encouraging cross-network collaboration to accelerate learning, best practice sharing and enterprise-wide opportunities and solutions.
- Through education and counsel, persuaded members of the Supply Chain organization to include the transgender community in the Supplier Diversity Program.
- Increased employee awareness of DEI and positioned the company as a leader in this area by proactively monitoring
  diversity best practices; sharing educational content to HR, Talent and Recruitment Teams and creating high traffic
  diversity articles used on Cox Enterprises' internal and external LinkedIn social media channel.

Infrastructure Engineer (2011-2015)
Windows Systems Administration (2005-2011)

### **EDUCATION & PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT**

Executive MBA; Organizational Leadership; Ashford University; San Diego, CA; 2019; GPA: 4.0 BS; Mass Communications; Brenau University; Gainesville, GA; 1997

• Minor, Electronic Mass Media

Georgia Institute of Technology; Data Analytics & Science Program; 2021; GPA: 4.0

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Data Analytics & Data Science, ITIL V3, VMware VCP5-DCV & VCA-DCV, Microsoft MCSA, Helpdesk Manager

#### **AFFILIATIONS**

Technology Association of Georgia (TAG)

Georgia Out Business Alliance: 2018 inaugural award recipient, Business Person of the Year